[
    {
        "title": "United States Landmark Supreme Court Cases",
        "test_id": 2,
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Brown v. board of Eduction",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "Separate But Equal",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Separate But Equal",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1954",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Plessy v. Ferguson",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "State-mandated segregation laws did not violate the equal protection clause of the fourth amendment.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "State-mandated segregation laws did not violate the equal protection clause of the fourth amendment.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1896",
        "hint_2": "Jim Crow laws are constitutional under this related doctrine",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Gibbons v. Ogden",
                "option_1": "When a federal and state law are in conflict, the federal law is supreme",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "When a federal and state law are in conflict, the federal law is supreme",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1824",
        "hint_2": "Congress and New York had both passed laws regulating the steamboat industry. ",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Dred Scott v. Sandford",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "The Constitution does not consider slaves to be U.S. citizens. Rather, they are constitutionally protected property of their masters.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "The Constitution does not consider slaves to be U.S. citizens. Rather, they are constitutionally protected property of their masters",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1857",
        "hint_2": "f “Once free, always free.”",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Schenck v. United States",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "Speech that presents a “clear and present danger” to the security of the United States is in violation of the principle of free speech as protected by the First Amendment to the Constitution.",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Speech that presents a “clear and present danger” to the security of the United States is in violation of the principle of free speech as protected by the First Amendment to the Constitution.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "The general secretary of the Socialist Party was arrested for distributing literature discouraging young men from enlisting in the armed forces. ",
        "hint_2": "1919",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Mapp v. Ohio",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "Evidence that is illegally obtained by the state may not be used against a defendant in court.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Evidence that is illegally obtained by the state may not be used against a defendant in court.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1961",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Engel v. Vitale",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": "Public institutions (i.e., a school system) cannot require prayer."
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Public institutions (i.e., a school system) cannot require prayer.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1962",
        "hint_2": "Athiest",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Miranda v. Arizona",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "You have the right to remain silent …",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "You have the right to remain silent …",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1966",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "San Antonio Independent School District v. Rodriguez",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "The Constitution does not guarantee a fundamental right to education",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "The Constitution does not guarantee a fundamental right to education",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1973",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Roe v. Wade",
                "option_1": "The Constitutionally implied right to privacy protects a woman’s choice in matters of abortion.",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "The Constitutionally implied right to privacy protects a woman’s choice in matters of abortion.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1973",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Hamer v. Campbell",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "The circuit clerk of Mississippi, for denying her and other Black people the right to register and vote.",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "The circuit clerk of Mississippi, for denying her and other Black people the right to register and vote.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Tinker v. Des Moines",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": " Does the First Amendment prohibit public school officials from barring students' from wearing black armbands to symbolize anti-war political protest?"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1969",
        "hint_2": "Make Love Not War!",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Loving v. Virginia",
                "option_1": "Laws banning interracial marriage violate the Equal Protection and Due Process Clauses of the Fourteenth Amendment to the U.S. Constitution.",
                "option_2": "The fundamental right to marry is guaranteed to same-sex couples by both the Due Process Clause and the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment to the United States Constitution.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Laws banning interracial marriage violate the Equal Protection and Due Process Clauses of the Fourteenth Amendment to the U.S. Constitution.",
        "option_2": "The fundamental right to marry is guaranteed to same-sex couples by both the Due Process Clause and the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment to the United States Constitution.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "1967",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Regents of the U. of California v. Bakke",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "A university's use of racial \"quotas\" in its admissions process was unconstitutional.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer":"a university's use of racial \"quotas\" in its admissions process was unconstitutional",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "This case explores the legal concept of equal protection.",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Obergefell v. Hodges",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": "Laws banning interracial marriage violate the Equal Protection and Due Process Clauses of the Fourteenth Amendment to the U.S. Constitution."
            }
        ],
        "answer": "Laws banning interracial marriage violate the Equal Protection and Due Process Clauses of the Fourteenth Amendment to the U.S. Constitution.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    },
    {
        "target": [
            {
                "question": "Griswold v. Connecticut",
                "option_1": "",
                "option_2": "A state's ban on the use of contraceptives violated the right to marital privacy.",
                "option_3": "",
                "option_4": ""
            }
        ],
        "answer": "A state's ban on the use of contraceptives violated the right to marital privacy.",
        "img": "",
        "points": 34,
        "hint_1": "",
        "hint_2": "",
        "hint_3": ""
    }
]